{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742354061","data":{"timestamp":" 947742354061"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e07f8a9e-7da5-45f8-bf94-d4b8bfeb8aef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742354284","data":{"timestamp":" 947742354284"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e07f8a9e-7da5-45f8-bf94-d4b8bfeb8aef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742355248","data":{"timestamp":" 947742355248"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e07f8a9e-7da5-45f8-bf94-d4b8bfeb8aef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742356523","data":{"timestamp":" 947742356522"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e07f8a9e-7da5-45f8-bf94-d4b8bfeb8aef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742359354","data":{"timestamp":" 947742359354"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e07f8a9e-7da5-45f8-bf94-d4b8bfeb8aef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742360196","data":{"timestamp":" 947742360196"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e07f8a9e-7da5-45f8-bf94-d4b8bfeb8aef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742360509","data":{"timestamp":" 947742360509"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e07f8a9e-7da5-45f8-bf94-d4b8bfeb8aef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742361742","data":{"timestamp":" 947742361742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e07f8a9e-7da5-45f8-bf94-d4b8bfeb8aef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742365223","data":{"timestamp":" 947742365223"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e07f8a9e-7da5-45f8-bf94-d4b8bfeb8aef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742366205","data":{"timestamp":" 947742366205"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e07f8a9e-7da5-45f8-bf94-d4b8bfeb8aef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742366458","data":{"timestamp":" 947742366458"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e07f8a9e-7da5-45f8-bf94-d4b8bfeb8aef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742367401","data":{"timestamp":" 947742367401"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e07f8a9e-7da5-45f8-bf94-d4b8bfeb8aef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742370209","data":{"timestamp":" 947742370209"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e07f8a9e-7da5-45f8-bf94-d4b8bfeb8aef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742371242","data":{"timestamp":" 947742371242"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e07f8a9e-7da5-45f8-bf94-d4b8bfeb8aef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742371715","data":{"timestamp":" 947742371715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e07f8a9e-7da5-45f8-bf94-d4b8bfeb8aef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742376221","data":{"timestamp":" 947742376221"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e07f8a9e-7da5-45f8-bf94-d4b8bfeb8aef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742376281","data":{"timestamp":" 947742376281"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e07f8a9e-7da5-45f8-bf94-d4b8bfeb8aef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742392343","data":{"timestamp":" 947742392342"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 833cf3c0-5f80-4483-8090-3d147bc48b68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742392566","data":{"timestamp":" 947742392566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 833cf3c0-5f80-4483-8090-3d147bc48b68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742392602","data":{"timestamp":" 947742392602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 833cf3c0-5f80-4483-8090-3d147bc48b68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742392671","data":{"timestamp":" 947742392671"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 833cf3c0-5f80-4483-8090-3d147bc48b68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742420332","data":{"timestamp":" 947742420332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 833cf3c0-5f80-4483-8090-3d147bc48b68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742432502","data":{"timestamp":" 947742432502"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 1fbadef2-b966-41b8-89ef-33c22badb48d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_6-9-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742439075","data":{"timestamp":" 947742439075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 1fbadef2-b966-41b8-89ef-33c22badb48d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-8-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742446431","data":{"timestamp":" 947742446430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 1fbadef2-b966-41b8-89ef-33c22badb48d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-8-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742455416","data":{"timestamp":" 947742455416"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 1fbadef2-b966-41b8-89ef-33c22badb48d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-7-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742471287","data":{"timestamp":" 947742471287"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 1fbadef2-b966-41b8-89ef-33c22badb48d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_6-7-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742479674","data":{"timestamp":" 947742479673"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 1fbadef2-b966-41b8-89ef-33c22badb48d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_6-2-1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742487222","data":{"timestamp":" 947742487222"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 1fbadef2-b966-41b8-89ef-33c22badb48d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_6-2-1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742491913","data":{"timestamp":" 947742491912"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 1fbadef2-b966-41b8-89ef-33c22badb48d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742497445","data":{"timestamp":" 947742497445"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 1fbadef2-b966-41b8-89ef-33c22badb48d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742504197","data":{"timestamp":" 947742504196"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 1fbadef2-b966-41b8-89ef-33c22badb48d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742512022","data":{"timestamp":" 947742512021"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 1fbadef2-b966-41b8-89ef-33c22badb48d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742541926","data":{"timestamp":" 947742541926"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 1fbadef2-b966-41b8-89ef-33c22badb48d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742548546","data":{"timestamp":" 947742548545"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 1fbadef2-b966-41b8-89ef-33c22badb48d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742563439","data":{"timestamp":" 947742563439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742578411","data":{"timestamp":" 947742578411"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742579646","data":{"timestamp":" 947742579645"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742587233","data":{"timestamp":" 947742587233"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ke"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742588627","data":{"timestamp":" 947742588627"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ke"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742604167","data":{"timestamp":" 947742604167"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ni"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742605235","data":{"timestamp":" 947742605235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ni"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742612771","data":{"timestamp":" 947742612771"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_su"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742613879","data":{"timestamp":" 947742613879"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_su"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742622328","data":{"timestamp":" 947742622328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_da"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742623898","data":{"timestamp":" 947742623898"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_da"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742634784","data":{"timestamp":" 947742634784"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ba"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742636239","data":{"timestamp":" 947742636239"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ba"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742646253","data":{"timestamp":" 947742646253"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742647566","data":{"timestamp":" 947742647565"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742654784","data":{"timestamp":" 947742654783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742656045","data":{"timestamp":" 947742656045"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742667994","data":{"timestamp":" 947742667994"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742669305","data":{"timestamp":" 947742669305"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742676658","data":{"timestamp":" 947742676658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742687475","data":{"timestamp":" 947742687475"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_yo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742688526","data":{"timestamp":" 947742688526"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_yo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742698909","data":{"timestamp":" 947742698909"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_yo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742706488","data":{"timestamp":" 947742706487"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" ba976218-378d-4e43-8e5e-ecd25700c95e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_syl.2ch..2ch..3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_yo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742716481","data":{"timestamp":" 947742716480"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e45d360c-347c-44df-9599-fd623875e837"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742716711","data":{"timestamp":" 947742716711"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e45d360c-347c-44df-9599-fd623875e837"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742717683","data":{"timestamp":" 947742717682"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e45d360c-347c-44df-9599-fd623875e837"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742718968","data":{"timestamp":" 947742718967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e45d360c-347c-44df-9599-fd623875e837"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742721868","data":{"timestamp":" 947742721867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e45d360c-347c-44df-9599-fd623875e837"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742722727","data":{"timestamp":" 947742722726"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e45d360c-347c-44df-9599-fd623875e837"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742723047","data":{"timestamp":" 947742723047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e45d360c-347c-44df-9599-fd623875e837"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742724294","data":{"timestamp":" 947742724293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e45d360c-347c-44df-9599-fd623875e837"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742727869","data":{"timestamp":" 947742727868"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e45d360c-347c-44df-9599-fd623875e837"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742728856","data":{"timestamp":" 947742728856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e45d360c-347c-44df-9599-fd623875e837"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742729115","data":{"timestamp":" 947742729114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e45d360c-347c-44df-9599-fd623875e837"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742730074","data":{"timestamp":" 947742730072"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e45d360c-347c-44df-9599-fd623875e837"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742732987","data":{"timestamp":" 947742732987"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e45d360c-347c-44df-9599-fd623875e837"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742734031","data":{"timestamp":" 947742734031"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e45d360c-347c-44df-9599-fd623875e837"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742734517","data":{"timestamp":" 947742734517"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e45d360c-347c-44df-9599-fd623875e837"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742739100","data":{"timestamp":" 947742739099"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e45d360c-347c-44df-9599-fd623875e837"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742739182","data":{"timestamp":" 947742739182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e45d360c-347c-44df-9599-fd623875e837"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.2ch..2ch.noShow..17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742752155","data":{"timestamp":" 947742752154"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" e45d360c-347c-44df-9599-fd623875e837"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742762368","data":{"timestamp":" 947742762368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 361fee79-2db6-4a3f-82d9-8ab2b54e4cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_6-9-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742768577","data":{"timestamp":" 947742768577"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 361fee79-2db6-4a3f-82d9-8ab2b54e4cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_6-2-1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742775658","data":{"timestamp":" 947742775657"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 361fee79-2db6-4a3f-82d9-8ab2b54e4cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742782860","data":{"timestamp":" 947742782860"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 361fee79-2db6-4a3f-82d9-8ab2b54e4cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-7-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742787327","data":{"timestamp":" 947742787327"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 361fee79-2db6-4a3f-82d9-8ab2b54e4cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742796206","data":{"timestamp":" 947742796206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 361fee79-2db6-4a3f-82d9-8ab2b54e4cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742802483","data":{"timestamp":" 947742802483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 361fee79-2db6-4a3f-82d9-8ab2b54e4cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742811718","data":{"timestamp":" 947742811717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 361fee79-2db6-4a3f-82d9-8ab2b54e4cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-8-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742817220","data":{"timestamp":" 947742817220"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 361fee79-2db6-4a3f-82d9-8ab2b54e4cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_6-7-5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742821743","data":{"timestamp":" 947742821742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 361fee79-2db6-4a3f-82d9-8ab2b54e4cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_5_6-7-5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:syl.2ch..2ch..3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742839768","data":{"timestamp":" 947742839767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 361fee79-2db6-4a3f-82d9-8ab2b54e4cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_5_6-7-5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947742845223","data":{"timestamp":" 947742845222"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_084538"," gameId":" 361fee79-2db6-4a3f-82d9-8ab2b54e4cb7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_5_6-7-5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}